newscom.com 2011-01-04

# Privacy Policy

Newscom collects and stores personal information from our customers. This information is mandatory in order to access the Newscom offering and includes such information as name, physical address, email address and personal content preferences. Note that Newscom does not sell any customer data to third parties.

For customers residing outside of the United States, and in countries where we work with 3rd party agent partners, Newscom may share your information with our agent partners in order to provide local customer service.

The Newscom registration form that you complete in order to gain access to our site contains personal data. Newscom may use this information for marketing purposes as it helps us identify the products that are most relevant to your needs.

Children  
You must be of 18 years of age in order to use the Newscom site. By using our site you are confirming that you meet the minimum agent requirement.

Sharing lightboxes  
When you share a lightbox, you will be required to supply Newscom with an email address. We will send the recipient a one-time email and we do not retain this information.

Auto-collected information  
Consistent with standard Internet practices, Newscom tracks and retains data related to various activities you may execute while on the Newscom site. This may include browser type, IP address, ISP, date/time stamp.

Cookies  
The Newscom site uses Cookies and each time you visit our site, a cookie (small file) is sent to your computer's hard drive. The Cookie only identifies the user's computer. We use these Cookies to help learn more about your preferences and therefore make the most of your experience on our site. Our Cookies may be used for holding login information and will expire when all instances of the browser are closed.

Legal Disclaimer  
By using Newscom.com you agree to the terms of this privacy policy. Newscom may update this policy and will post the updated version to Newscom.com. Your continued use of Newscom.com shall constitute your acceptance of such revised privacy policy.

For questions about our privacy policy, please contact [support@newscom.com](mailto:support@newscom.com). If you would like to change, modify or update your personal information associated with your Newscom account, please send an email to [support@newscom.com](mailto:support@newscom.com).
